SEHRIBAN CHENG

415-349-6417

sehribancheng@yahoo.com/ linkedin.com/in/sehribancheng/ github.com/sgc88

SKILLS

JavaScript, jQuery, React, Express, Node.js, MongoDB, RubyOnRails, postgreSQL, Heroku, GitHub

SUMMARY

Junior Web Developer with background of eleven years of experience in finance and customer service

Curious and learning-focused on new technology, languages and frameworks.

Strong communication and ability to facilitate conflict resolution from leadership positions.

Collaborate with various professionals to maximize performance in facilitating goals and attaining operational excellence.

PROJECTS

EventsApp-RubyOnRails, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, gem 'simple-calendar', gem 'acts_as_votable, bycrpt, activerecord.

DreamTrip: It is a planning and organizing web based application for your traveling needs. -HTML, javaScript, jQueryCSS Bootstrap MongoDB, Mongoose, PassportJS, NodeJS, ExpressJs, EJS templating.

Basil:Basil solves the problem of finding recipes based off of the ingredients that you have available at home Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Javascript / jQuery, Spoonacular API, HTTParty, Bootstrap, Bcrypt.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Citibank - Personal Banker/ Officer/ Assistant Branch Manager 05/2015-06/2017-

- -Managed a team of 8 to run successfully day to day operations.
- -Communicated with internal department to troubleshot website issues.
- -Won Citibank awards for being 1st and 2nd meeting San Francisco area branches.

YapiKredi Bank, Istanbul, Corporate Banking Director Turkey 2004 - 2012

- -Effectively communicated with major multinational corporations regarding loans, foreign exchange, derivatives and bonds.
- -Conducted informative, engaging presentations to new & existing clientele.

EDUCATION

General Assembly Full Stack Web Development 09/2017- 12/2017

Lincoln University-MBA of **Finance Management & Investment Banking** 02/2012-12/2014 Karadeniz Technical University - **Economics** 2000-2004